Guide to the Carl and Shelley Smith Mydans Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1942-2000; Series II; 35.42; (35 boxes)
  - U.S.S.R. (2 of 2) (Box 116)
  - Grenada--Schultz coverage, February 1984 (Box 116)
  - Korea (Box 116)
  - Korean War, Carl Mydans (Box 116)
  - Korea: International Cultural Society: Dr. Kim (Box 116)
  - Indochina: the spreading war (Box 116)
  - Provoo Case (Box 116)
  - The Hugh Robinson Saga (Santo Tomas) (Box 117)
  - Songs: war vintages (Box 117)
  - The Philippines Elections: background, clippings, notes, people, during our visit, 1986 (Box 117)
  - Philippines: after Seth's arrival in 1985 and elections, etc. (Box 117)
  - Philippines, general (Box 117)
  - Philippines: memoirs, flashbacks (Box 117)
  - Philippines 1988-1993 (Box 117)
  - Philippines: The 1986 elections (Box 117)
  - Philippines, March 1989 (Box 117)
  - The Philippine Campaign (Box 117)
  - War in the Pacific (WWII) (Box 117)
  - Philippines elections--TIME and Newsweek stories, 1986 (Box 117)
  - Flashbacks from my war files on the Philippines to be considered for the memoir, September 1989 (Box 117)
  - U.S.S. Missouri (Box 117)
  - War in the Pacific--Bill Chickering (Box 117)
  - Marni Sandweiss: Mead Art Museum, Amherst College, 1990-1991 (Box 117)
  - Marni Sandweiss/Amon Carter Exhibition, 1985-1997 (Box 117)
  - Marni Sandweiss and Amon Carter correspondence, 1985-1994 (Box 117)
  - National Archives reproductions (Box 117)
  - Clippings: Easter Island research (Box 117)
  - Father Sebastian (Box 117)
  - Galapagos (Box 117)
  - Metei prepared material (Easter Island Expedition) (Box 117)
  - Easter Island text and criticism, 1965 (Box 117)
  - Easter Island captions, 1965 (Box 117)
  - Dr. Stanley Skoryna (Box 117)
  - Maureen and Richard Roberts, 1986 (Box 117)
  - Peter Beighton, 1965 (Box 117)
  - Easter Island "Newsletters", 1965 (Box 117)
  - Easter Island, Chilean documents (Box 117)
  - Easter Island: documents, stamps, etc. (Box 117)
  - Easter Island: notes and correspondence, 1965-1985 (Box 117)
  - Easter Island: references to books and my notes (Box 117)
  - Easter Island: planning for..., 1964 (Box 117)
  - One Hundred Years of Christianity and Primer Siglo Cristiano de la Isla de Pascua by Father Sebastian Englert, 1968 (Box 117)
  - Easter Island: novel (Box 117)
  - Easter Island: research, 8 (Box 118)
  - Ethnology of Easter Island by Alfred Metraux (Box 118)
  - Amazon (Box 118)
  - Suriname (Box 118)
  - Argentina (Box 118)
  - Azores (Box 118)
  - Belize (once British Honduras), 2 (Box 118)
  - Bolivia (Box 118)
  - Bermuda (Box 118)
  - Brazil (Box 118)
  - Caribbean (Box 118)
  - Chile (Box 118)
  - Colombia (Box 118)
  - Central America (Box 118)
  - Costa Rica (Box 118)
  - Cuba (Box 118)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 119)
  - Ecuador (Box 119)
  - El Salvador (Box 119)
  - Guam (Box 119)
  - Guatemala (Box 119)
  - French Guiana (Box 119)
  - Guerrillas & terror (Box 119)
  - Haiti (Box 119)
  - Honduras (Box 119)
  - Latin America (Box 119)
  - Guyana (Box 119)
  - Nicaragua (Box 119)
  - Paraguay (Box 119)
  - Panama (Box 119)
  - Peru (Box 119)
  - Puerto Rico, Virgin Islands (Box 119)
  - Suriname (Box 119)
  - Uruguay (Box 119)
  - Yucatan (Box 119)
  - Venezuela (Box 119)
  - Vietnam: the war--its history (Box 119)
  - Mexico--West Coast--Prime Time, 3 (Box 119)
  - Mexico (Box 119)
  - TIME, Inc., early section (Box 119)
  - Pictures: TIME and Newsweek covers on Soviet breakup artists (Box 119)
  - Florida (Box 119)
  - El Paso-Juarez (Box 120)
  - San Francisco, October 21-November 2 '79, 1979 (Box 120)
  - Egypt (Box 120)
  - California housing and maps (Box 120)
  - California stories (Box 120)
  - Malaria and the mosquito (Box 120)
  - Caviar/sturgeon (Box 120)
  - Fish: fugu and poison fish (Box 120)
  - California (Box 120)
  - United States, 2 (Box 120)
  - TIME, Inc., Washington, 1985; 2 (Box 120)
  - What's Doing In (Box 120)
  - Medical (Box 120)
  - New York (Box 120)
  - Fish: general, 2 (Box 120)
  - Fish: fish farming (Box 121)
  - Fish: eels (Box 121)
  - Fish: shad (Box 121)
  - National Fisherman (Box 121)
  - Texas (Box 121)
  - Shell Fish: clams, oysters, shrimp, mussels, lobsters, etc. (Box 121)
  - Burma Dance story for Smithsonian (Box 121)
  - Bali (Box 121)
  - Bali text and Bali clips, 2 (Box 121)
  - Pagan story, 1974; 2 (Box 121)
  - Orangutans, 2 (Box 121)
  - Bomb test at Yucca Flat, 1952 April 22; 2 (Box 121)
  - Chinatown--Singapore (Box 121)
  - Singapore--Chinatown (rough text and captions) (Box 121)
  - Chinatown: text and captions (Box 121)
  - India trip, 1974 October 23-November 6 (Box 121)
  - Malaysia: Taman Negara National Park (Box 121)
  - The Mai story (Ansbach) (Box 121)
  - Magsaysay Awards/Rockefeller/Ravenholdt (Box 121)
  - Leathery turtle: research, 2 (Box 121)
  - Leathery turtle: correspondence (Box 121)
  - Chinatown--Singapore: clippings and Lim Kim Guan's reports, 2 (Box 121)
  - Orangutan text, 1973 (Box 121)
  - Giant leathery turtle: final draft (Box 121)
  - Burma Dance, 4 (Box 122)
  - Mydans: misc. photographs and exhibitions (Box 122)
  - Langkawi Country Club (Box 122)
  - Coconut oil, 2 (Box 122)
  - China: reforestation (Box 122)
  - Defoliation, rome plow, destruction of the land of Vietnam (Box 122)
  - Published magazine stories, 1976 (Box 122)
  - Burma Dangers: text and captions (Box 122)
  - PrimeTime: Mexico's West Coast captions (Box 122)
  - Completed Smithsonian stories, 1973 (Box 122)
  - The Negev and Sinai--clips (Box 122)
  - Peradeniya Royal Botanic Gardens, Kandy District: text and research (Box 122)
  - Rotan--flogging, capital punishment, 2 (Box 122)
  - Prisoners and prison camps, 2 (Box 122)
  - Prisoners of war: general (Box 122)
  - Prisoners of war, especially Vietnam period, 1969-1972; 2 (Box 122)
  - Prisoners of war: research and text for "Three Came Home" (Box 122)
  - Prisoners of war: Japan Conflict and general (Box 122)
  - Arctic and Antarctic Dew Line, 2 (Box 122)
  - Hysteria of war, rumor (Box 122)
  - Desert: Yuma, Arizona. Desert story, 1964 (Box 122)
  - Micronesia: Frank McCulloch's file (Bikini) (Box 122)
  - Sturgeon--caviar, 2 (Box 122)
  - Shelters (Box 123)
  - Transcontinental trucking (Box 123)
  - "The Deputy" (Box 123)
  - "Delilah" by Marcus Goodrich (Box 123)
  - U.S. Customs (Box 123)
  - Manuel (Manda) Elizalde: text piece, etc. (Box 123)
  - China, 3 (Box 123)
  - Taking pictures in China, 2 (Box 123)
  - China 1978: Shelley's research and notes on Lindblad China trip, 2 (Box 123)
  - Captions for China Drum (Box 123)
  - China captions, 2 (Box 123)
  - Shanghai captions from various LIFE photographers' sets in post-war Shanghai until its 1949 fall (Box 123)
  - TIME China story: domestic and Asia (Box 123)
  - China: early and later periods: a consolidation after September 1972 wedding (Box 123)
  - China years (Box 123)
  - China trip: papers, documents, visa instructions, copies of visa applications, etc., 1978 August (Box 123)
  - China trip: cameras and film, 1978 August (Box 123)
  - China: captions and Mike's first drafts and Shelley's check points, 1978 September (Box 123)
  - China: important overall clipping folder (Box 123)
  - China, 1969-1971 (Box 123)
  - China story: captions, 1978 August (Box 123)
  - China permissions (Box 123)
  - China: First Emperor's 6000 pottery man and horse army, Terracotta Army, near Sian (Xi'an) (Box 123)
  - China: since ping pong, 1972 January (Box 123)
  - Overseas Chinese Businessmen: clips and research taken on story (Box 123)
  - China, 1978-1979; 2 (Box 124)
  - Overseas Chinese in Southeast Asia (Box 124)
  - Overseas Chinese Businessmen story: captions (Box 124)
  - Michael Blumenthal (Shanghai, etc.) (Box 124)
  - Tokyo (Box 124)
  - Rice (Box 124)
  - Bath (Box 124)
  - Bacteriological warfare (Box 124)
  - Bamboo (Box 124)
  - Birth (Box 124)
  - Dancing (Box 124)
  - Dead, funerals (Japanese) (Box 124)
  - Dependent housing (Box 124)
  - Dress (Box 124)
  - Divorce (Box 124)
  - Early Japan (Box 124)
  - ETA (Box 124)
  - Festivals (Box 124)
  - Food (Box 124)
  - Geisha (Box 124)
  - Historical background: feudalistic, characteristics, etc. (Box 124)
  - Imperial household (Box 124)
  - Pearl (Box 124)
  - Suicides (Box 124)
  - Salt (Box 124)
  - Silk (Box 124)
  - Swords (Box 124)
  - Tattooing (Box 124)
  - Tourist (Box 124)
  - Tea (Box 124)
  - Tradition (Box 124)
  - Juvenile delinquency (Box 124)
  - Hydroponic (Box 124)
  - Fiction (Box 124)
  - Customs and manners, 4 (Box 124)
  - "Off Beat" (Box 124)
  - Prostitution (Box 124)
  - Prisoner of War (Box 124)
  - Women (Box 124)
  - Language, 2 (Box 124)
  - Marriage, 2 (Box 124)
  - Love (Box 124)
  - American attitudes toward Japanese (Box 125)
  - My written things on photography (Box 125)
  - Photojournalism presentation, first batch, four each, 1980 (Box 125)
  - Photography text (Box 125)
  - Captions for Geographic and Fotofusion, Delray Beach, Florida, 1997January 28 - February 1 (Box 125)
  - Travel with camera (Box 125)
  - Lecturing: slide presentation: some of my previous talks (Box 125)
  - Slide presentations: China, ASMP, Boston University Retrospective, 1985 (Box 125)
  - Dick Pollard, 1989 (Box 125)
  - Correspondence--Photojournalism issue, 1989 (Box 125)
  - Photojournalism issue: the Washington reception, 1989 (Box 125)
  - "Photography: a Revolution in Communications" lecture. Original. (Box 125)
  - Notable photographers, 2 (Box 125)
  - The photojournalist (Box 125)
  - Photojournalism (Box 125)
  - The Camera as Persuader: BBC, Martina Hall, Claire Beavan (to interview) (Box 125)
  - War photographers (Box 125)
  - Light (Box 125)
  - Chester Higgins Jr. (Box 125)
  - Photography: The Model (Box 125)
  - American Photographer (Sean Callahan) (Box 125)
  - Cameras and Film (Box 125)
  - Nikon Action Touch camera manual (Box 125)
  - Cameras (Box 125)
  - LIFE--new (Box 125)
  - How to take pictures (Box 125)
  - Lane and Anna Stewart (Box 125)
  - War correspondents (Box 126)
  - Self image and having your picture taken (Box 126)
  - TIME photojournalism page (Box 126)
  - Other publication, projects, picture releases, and rates (Box 126)
  - Photography: general (Box 126)
  - Photography: Hugh Moffett's judgments (Box 126)
  - Japanese cameras and their history (Box 126)
  - Camera: from ringed notebooks, copies of notations on "Cameras and Photography" (Box 126)
  - TIME photographers on old TIME roto listing (Box 126)
  - New magazines on photojournalism (Box 126)
  - Retrospective and book: comments and press notices, 2 (Box 126)
  - Retrospective and xeroxes of jackets from which negatives have been taken and grouped (Box 126)
  - Amon Carter press release, 1986; 2 (Box 126)
  - Amon Carter Museum exhibition, 1986 (Box 126)
  - Forward of Carl Mydans, Photojournalist by Carl Mydans (Box 126)
  - Introduction by Philip B. Kunhardt, "Talking to Carl Mydans" (Box 126)
  - Holland McCombs (Box 126)
  - The Picture Collection: Miki Dunn's report, 1976-1983 (Box 126)
  - Robert Cantwell (Box 126)
  - Mike Spindler (Lotta Eherenberg), 1964 (Box 126)
  - The Mais/Germany, 1983 (Box 126)
  - Amon Carter Museum (Box 126)
  - Circle Fine Art Corporation (Barry Podgorsky), 1991-1995 (Box 126)
  - Circle--New Orleans (Box 126)
  - Circle print prices (Box 126)
  - Circle Fine Art Corp., Chicago, May 11-14, 1993 (Box 126)
  - Circle Fine Art Corporation, San Francisco (Nov. 20-Nov. 25, 1991) (Box 126)
  - Circle Gallery, Costa Mesa, June 20-23, 1995 (Box 126)
  - SoHo Circle Gallery exhibition, 1994 (Box 127)
  - Circle Gallery, Washington show (Box 127)
  - Circle Gallery: ringed notes copies (Box 127)
  - Circle Fine Art: general (Box 127)
  - Circle Galleries, beginning Joseph Atkin period, 1996 (Box 127)
  - Circle Gallery: San Francisco, the first of the new year, 1996 (Box 127)
  - Martha's Vineyard 1996 exhibition (Box 127)
  - Circle Gallery: Toronto, 1996 (Box 127)
  - Circle Fine Art: San Diego, 1992 (Box 127)
  - Solomon and Solomon, 1996 (Box 127)
  - Circle Gallery: San Diego, 1995 (Box 127)
  - Circle Fine Art: San Diego (Box 127)
  - Perpignan clippings, 1994 (Box 127)
  - Perpignan: International Festival, 7 to 15 September, 1991, photojournalism, Jean François Leroy (Box 127)
  - Perpignan clippings (Box 127)
  - Perpignan--Visa pour L'Image 8 e 8th, 1996 (Box 127)
  - Perpignan, 1994 (Box 127)
  - Perpignan, 1997 (Box 127)
  - Cameras technical data (Box 127)
  - Clippings: Visa pour L'Image 6 (Box 127)
  - Perpignan--7, 1995 (Box 127)
  - Perpignan, 1994 (Box 127)
  - Eddie Adams Workshop, 1989 (Box 127)
  - The Eddie Adams workshop and other workshops, 1988 (Box 127)
  - Eddie Adams workshop, 1990 (Box 127)
  - Eddie Adams workshop, 1991 (Box 127)
  - Pepignan: Jean Francois Leroy, Sylvie Grumbach, 1994 (Box 127)
  - Eddie Adams workshop, 1993; 2 (Box 127)
  - Eddie Adams workshop, 1994 (Box 127)
  - Eddie Adams workshop, 1995 (Box 127)
  - Eddie Adams workshop, 1996 (Box 127)
  - Eddie Adams (Box 128)
  - Eddie Adams workshop, 1995 (Box 128)
  - Eddie Adams workshop, October 11-14, 1996, Barnstorm the 9th (Box 128)
  - Eddie Adams workshop: Barnstorm the 10th, 1997 (Box 128)
  - POW's, Operation Homecoming, Clark Field, etc., 1973 (Box 128)
  - Undeveloped film (Box 128)
  - Vietnam: refugees, 1968 Tet Offensive, my file, exchange of cables, captions, and refugees general (Box 128)
  - Eddie Adams, 1997 (Box 128)
  - "More Than Meets the Eye": reviews and comments (Box 129)
  - "More Than Meets the Eye": mail queries (Box 129)
  - "More Than Meets the Eye": Evan Thomas' reaction to cut manuscript (Box 129)
  - "More Than Meets the Eye": early notes and letters (Box 129)
  - "More Than Meets the Eye": deletions, 1990 (Box 129)
  - "More Than Meets the Eye": reprints, etc. (Box 129)
  - "More Than Meets the Eye": original manuscript returned by printer, 2 (Box 129)
  - "More Than Meets the Eye": second carbon clean typed manuscript, 2 (Box 129)
  - "More Than Meets the Eye": as prepared for final typing (Box 130)
  - Santo Tomas posters (Box 130)
  - Taylor, Warren. "The Voyage of the U.S.S. Sarasota" (Box 130)
  - Lucas, Celia. "Prisoners of Santo Tomas," xerox of book (Box 130)
  - Taylor, Warren. "The Voyage of the U.S.S. Sumner from December 7, 1941 to May 27, 1944" (Box 130)
  - Yokohama Trials, 1947; 6 (Box 130)
  - Dang, Donald M. "Survival in Santo Tomas" (Box 130)
  - Ministry of Defense. "Treatment of British Prisoners of War in Korea", 1955 (Box 130)
  - The United States Strategic Bombing Survey. "Effects of Air Attack on Urban Complex Tokyo-Kawasaki-Yokohama", 1947 (Box 130)
  - The United States Strategic Bombing Survey. "The Effects of Atomic Bombs on Hiroshima and Nagasaki", 1946 (Box 130)
  - United States Strategic Bombing Survey. "Summary Report (Pacific War)", 1946 (Box 130)
  - The United States Strategic Bombing Survey. "The Effects of Bombing on Health and Medical Services in Japan", 1947 (Box 130)
  - The United States Strategic Bombing Survey. "The Effects of Strategic Bombing on Japanese Morale", 1947 (Box 130)
  - The United States Bombing Survey. "Japan's Struggle to End the War", 1946 (Box 130)
  - Cohen, Bernard and Maurice Cooper. "A Follow-Up Study of World War II Prisoners of War", 1954 (Box 130)
  - The Yalis of the Bosphorus (Box 131)
  - Pictures of Yali (Box 131)
  - Istanbul and Bosphorus: research (Box 131)
  - Yalis: copies, text, and captions (Box 131)
  - Yalis: to send magazine (Box 131)
  - Yali of the Bosphorus: story suggestion and correspondence with Smithsonian (Box 131)
  - Material for captions (Box 131)
  - The Yalis of the Bosphorus: manuscript (Box 131)
  - Yali of the Bosphorus: research material, 4 (Box 131)
  - Turkey Trip, 1983 (Box 131)
  - Trip to Turkey: travel plans, 1983 (Box 131)
  - Istanbul: clippings (Box 131)
  - Turkey (Box 131)
  - Envelope (Box 131)
  - Smithsonian Exhibit and Panel--WWII, 1994 (Box 131)
  - Smithsonian Institution: loaned objects, 1994 (Box 131)
  - Library of America: Reporting World War II, Max Rudin, 1995 (Box 131)
  - LIFE: Pearl Harbor Day, Jan Mason, 1991 (Box 131)
  - John Toland, 1987-1997 (Box 131)
  - CEL Communications, Inc. (Corporate Entertaining & Learning), 1991 (Box 131)
  - Chizu Omori: Film on Japanese Relocation Centers, 1993 (Box 131)
  - Tom and Carolyn Griffith, 1990-1992 (Box 131)
  - LIFE: The Second Decade, United Technologies, trip to Washington, 1985 (Box 131)
  - Mike Bessie, "Theodore H. White At Large", 1991 (Box 131)
  - Parade (magazine): Larry Smith, Walter Anderson, 1997 (Box 131)
  - Howard and Virginia Sloane, 1997 (Box 131)
  - Tina Ruisinger, photographer. "The Faces of Photography", 1998 (Box 131)
  - Wennerstrom: The camera trips the master... (Box 131)
  - Espionage and National Security, 2 (Box 132)
  - Christopher Rand (Box 132)
  - Murray Fromson (Box 132)
  - Richard Clurman (Box 132)
  - James Agee (Box 132)
  - Terry H. Anderson, prisoners (Box 132)
  - FYI, 1991 (Box 132)
  - Washington trip for Esther Crane's 90th birthday, 1992 (Box 132)
  - Picture Post, 1994 (Box 132)
  - Albert and Marjorie Ravenholt, 1986-1994 (Box 132)
  - JB Pictures, Jocelyn Benzakin, 1993 (Box 132)
  - Naythons, Matthew. "The Face of Mercy", 1992 (Box 132)
  - Peter Arnett (Box 132)
  - Overseas Press Club, 1989 (Box 132)
  - "The Camera Goes to War," Steve Smith, Videosmiths, 1993 (Box 132)
  - Karen Mullarkey, NHK, 1994 (Box 132)
  - Americanization of the Scillags (Box 132)
  - Ed and Lee Thompson (Box 132)
  - LIFE: Sasha Nyary (bioperse) (Box 132)
  - Erin Whelan (Box 132)
  - Carl's return to war after exchange (Box 132)
  - Washington Scene (Box 132)
  - LIFE: The Second Decade, Varied Directions, Inc., 1985 (Box 132)
  - Phil Kunhardt (Box 132)
  - Ken Cuthbertson: on Emily Hahn and Hong Kong (Liberation Voyage 1943) (Box 132)
  - Billy Graham (Box 132)
  - Linda and Jack Vartoogian (Box 132)
  - Dick and Gail Hoffman (Box 132)
  - Smithsonian Magazine, Ed Thompson (Box 132)
  - ASMP (Box 132)
  - Massimo Calabresi (Box 132)
  - Nikon (Box 132)
  - Shelley Diamond, Capital Cities, ABC, 1995 (Box 132)
  - Crissy Walford (Box 132)
  - Newsweek (Box 132)
  - Elna Wilkinson (Box 132)
  - John Bradley and Jean MacArthur (Box 132)
  - Deanna Bonner-Ganter (Box 132)
  - Evan Kriss, New York Times, 1994 (Box 132)
  - Sari Henry, 1994 (Box 132)
  - Joanne Palulian (Box 132)
  - Henry Grunwald, 1996 (Box 132)
  - Bill Hooper, TIME, Inc. Research Center (Box 132)
  - Kimberlee Acquaro (Box 132)
  - Margi Lang (Box 132)
  - John Peterson (Arthur Rothstein), 1997 (Box 132)
  - Bobbie Baker Burrows (Box 132)
  - The Meisters: Denmark (Box 132)
  - Hugh and Penny Brown, 1996 (Box 132)
  - Claire Yaffa, 1997 (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: during and after the Tet Offensive, 1968 (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: general selections for my 1968 Vietnam visit (Box 132)
  - National Liberation Front and the Viet Cong, Hanoi Command (Box 132)
  - Scorched Earth, pacification (Box 132)
  - Vietnam, air-sea rescue (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: delta warfare, gunships, river warfare (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: deep patrolling, background and eyewitness (Mannock) (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: the kind of war, 1976 (Box 132)
  - Vietnam, 1954-1965 (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: Pentagon Papers, The New York Times report of its causes, June 1971 (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: also Cholon, the Chinese City and the shooting of the Chinese blackmarketer, 1966 (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: eyewitness reports (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: "Sin City"--the brothels (Box 132)
  - Vietnam, 1967 (Box 132)
  - Vietnam, 1970 (Box 132)
  - Hanson Baldwin (Viet Nam) (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: selection sent to Seth in 1972 and returned in July 1972 (Box 132)
  - Vietnam: Tet Offensive, investigative report by Carl Mydans, also cable exchanges, questions asked for LIFE report, 1968 (Box 132)
  - Gedeon de Margitay, foreign books and syndication, 1968-1970 (Box 132)
  - Rich Clarkson, The Steamboat Workshops, Steamboat Springs Art Council (Box 132)
  - Current correspondents, 1998 (Box 133)
  - Cal and Sally Whipple (Box 133)
  - Eastman Kodak (Box 133)
  - Exhibition: Midtown Manhattan ICP (Box 133)
  - Florida exhibition (Box 133)
  - Lectures and selected references for lectures (Box 133)
  - Carrie Ross Welch (Box 133)
  - Conde Nast (Box 133)
  - Max Frankel, 1995 (Box 133)
  - San Diego exhibition, 1997 (Box 133)
  - Fotofusion, Delray Beach, Florida, Arnold Drapkin, Fatima NeJame (Box 133)
  - Early Years (Box 133)
  - Miriam Winocour, 1998 (Box 133)
  - John Durniak (Box 133)
  - Tristan de Cunha and Luce, also other Luce notes (Box 133)
  - Arnold Drapkin and Russian project, the Stevens and the Soviet Union (Box 133)
  - Yukiko Launois, 1993 (Box 133)
  - Clifton and Nancy Forster, Hawaii Loa College (Box 133)
  - Sidney S. Monroe, Soho Triad Fine arts, 1997 (Box 133)
  - Soho Triad Fine Arts: Barry Podgorsky, Monica Pollock, Sidney Monroe (Box 133)
  - Indonesia seminar talks (Box 133)
  - Galleries, exhibitions and collections (Box 133)
  - Inge Heckel, Metropolitan Museum of Art, "William" (The Red Balloon), A Tale of Two Williams (Box 133)
  - Tokyo for the book and the exhibition, August 8 through 16, 1995 (Box 133)
  - 90th birthday at TIME, Inc., 1997 (Box 133)
  - China book with Michael Demarest (Box 133)
  - China: A Visual Adventure: letters and reviews (Box 133)
  - China: A Visual Adventure: Simon & Schuster agreement (Box 133)
  - Annalee Jacoby Fadiman, 1997 (Box 133)
  - Vicki Goldberg, 1985 (Box 133)
  - Book and author lunches (Box 133)
  - Gloucester: A Day in the Life of America (Box 133)
  - National Geographic--Tom Kennedy (Box 133)
  - National Geographic seminar, 1990 (Box 133)
  - Misc. clippings and correspondence, 2 (Box 133)
  - Letters (Box 133)
  - TIME Magazine cover composite (Box 133)
  - Halstead, Dirck. "The Digital Journalist", 1998 (Box 133)
  - Letters of sympathy to Carl (Box 133)
  - Gordon Parks (Box 133)
  - LIFE (Box 134)
  - David and Nancy Friend, LIFE (Box 134)
  - Claire Daniel (Box 134)
  - Jennie Hirschfeld (Box 134)
  - Professional people (Box 134)
  - John Morris, 1997 (Box 134)
  - Lillian Fuentes, 1996 (Box 134)
  - Mills, Angie and Phoebe White Wentworth. "Fair Is the Name" (Box 134)
  - Trees, Greg Geisler (Box 134)
  - Linden Gross, Readers Digest (Box 134)
  - A Florida Fusion exhibition, 1997 (Box 134)
  - Santa Fe (Box 134)
  - The Photography Show, 1995 (Box 134)
  - Miscellaneous, unfiled (Box 134)
  - Vanity Fair, 2001 (Box 134)
  - New York Times Magazine, 1995 (Box 134)
  - LIFE: The Eisie Issue (Box 134)
  - LIFE: U.S. Camera (Box 134)
  - Code One, 2000 (Box 134)
  - Camera and Darkroom, 1994 (Box 134)
  - Photo: Le Programme Official, 1991 (Box 134)
  - Photo: Le Programme Official, 1996 (Box 134)
  - Misc. (Box 134)
  - Letters to the Soho Triad, 1997 (Box 134)
  - Letter from Mayor Giuliani, 1997 (Box 134)
  - Letters and cards received from Parade story, 1997 (Box 134)
  - Farm Security Administration, 1994; 4 (Box 134)
  - Roy Stryker, 2 (Box 134)
  - Farm Security Administration: unplanned ingathering (Box 134)
  - Farm Security: early years (Box 134)
  - Ray Bearse: correspondence and his book (Box 134)
  - Images of the Heartland, 1980 (Box 134)
  - Farm Security Administration clippings and stories (Box 134)
  - Greenbelt Towns, 1946 (Box 134)
  - National Geographic seminars, 1988 (Box 134)
  - Some records of my prints and exhibition pictures (Box 134)
  - Exhibition: 28th floor, Time and LIFE building (Box 134)
  - New York Times, topping (Box 134)
  - Joe Fromm (Box 134)
  - John and D. Lee Rich (Box 134)
  - Gerald M. Levin (Jeannette P. Lerman), 1994 (Box 134)
  - Readers Digest, Ed Thompson (Box 134)
  - Louis Kraar (Box 134)
  - Roy Rowan (Box 134)
  - Keyes and Yuko and Hannah Beech (Box 134)
  - Lester Bernstein (Box 134)
  - Bill Schuman (Box 135)
  - TIME: Kissinger (Box 135)
  - Book reviewing (Box 135)